FARIZ EZA SYAUQI

Front End Developer

syauqieza@gmail.com | 0822 1010 0609

CAREER SUMMARY:

I am a professional Web Developer with 2 years of experience of creating and developing a website or web app mostly with React and Laravel. I like building new stuff and work with other people. Highly skilled in communication, collaboration, and problem solving.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

PT Yokesen Teknologi Indonesia

Head of Engineering | October, 2021- Present

- Ensure the development process goes well according to the project timeline.
- Develop Gudangin, a cloud warehouse website for managing orders, stock
- Working closely and collaboratively with PM and Back-end in every project

Front End Developer | September, 2020 - October, 2021

- Build a Front End UI in every project based from Figma
- Develop Club Sobat Badak, a website for community
- Develop Warisan, a website for resellers
- Develop BKPI, a work report platform for the client
- Develop a lot of Landing Page for company campaign
- Develop more small project
- Working closely and collaboratively with PM and Back-end in every project

PT Core Mediatech

Database Administrator | June, 2016 - October, 2019

- Maintain Internal Database
- Maintain Internal Website
- Create a monthly invoice and reports for the customers
- Assisted troubleshooting software.

EDUCATION:

2019- 2020 | Purwadhika Startup & Coding School

Web & Mobile Development Bootcamp

2011- 2016 | Gunadarma University

Bachelor of Information System

SKILLS:

Programming Languages JavaScript (ES6), HTML,

JavaScript (ES6), HTN CSS/Sass, PHP

Library & Frameworks

jQuery, React, Next JS, Node.js, Express, Laravel

Tools & Platform

Git, Netlify, Vercel, Pusher